Guide to the Associated Students of Stanford University Records SC0009
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Associated Students of Stanford University records
1891-2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Associated Students of Stanford University.
SC0009
112.5 Linear Feet (154 boxes)
The records include correspondence, minutes, reports, financial records, and other materials arranged in the following series: President's Correspondence (1919-1971), Legislative Records (1891-1998), Student Manager (1924-1963), Treasurer (1939-1992), General Files (1936-1992), Organizations (1925-1990), Course Guides (1965-1980), and Additional Records (1984-2006).
Information about Access
The collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU) was organized in October 1891; each registered student is a member. The ASSU works to represent the interests, needs and perspectives of Stanford students.
Description of the Collection
The records include correspondence, minutes, reports, financial records, and other materials arranged in the following series: President's Correspondence (1919-1971), Legislative Records (1891-1998), Student Manager (1924-1963), Treasurer (1939-1992), General Files (1936-1992), Organizations (1925-1990), Course Guides (1965-1980), and Additional Records (1984-2006).
College student government.; College students.; Associated Students of Stanford University.; Associated Students of Stanford University.
- Presidents' Records, Series 1
  Scope and Contents note
  The President's records consist largely of correspondence but also include some reports, memoranda, agenda, minutes, and other materials. Typical subjects include athletics, social events (concerts, dances, etc.), the Honor Code and Fundamental Standard, ASSU elections and committee meetings, public service and philanthropy efforts (often filed under "Drives"), the student union, and relations with student governments at other universities. Stanford agencies often represented in the records include Stanford Alumni Association, Stanford Fund (and other fundraising groups), Dean of Men, Dean of Women, Dean of Students, President's Office, other student associations (such as the Interfraternity Council, Institute for International Relations, KZSU, and Ram's Head), and the Stanford Bookstore. There is also frequently correspondence with the National Student Federation of America (1930s-1940s), the National Students Association (1950s-1960s), the Pacific Student Presidents Association, and the World Student Service Fund (1940s). Finally, there are unique subjects relevant to the historic era: Civil Defense during World War II and the political unrest of the 1960s-1970s.
  - William Corbus (1932-33), Gerald H. Trautman (1933-34), Marvin R. Kahn (1934-35), 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Wallace S. Brooke, Incoming A-H, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Wallace S. Brooke, Incoming I-R, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Wallace S. Brooke, Incoming S-Z, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Wallace S. Brooke, Outgoing, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ralph "Jim" Reynolds, Incoming A-E, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ralph "Jim" Reynolds, Incoming F-M, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ralph "Jim" Reynolds, Incoming N, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ralph "Jim" Reynolds, Incoming N (cont.), 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ralph "Jim" Reynolds, Incoming O-R, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ralph "Jim" Reynolds, Incoming S-Z, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ralph "Jim" Reynolds, Outgoing, 1936 Aug.-1937 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Ralph "Jim" Reynolds, Outgoing, 1937 March-June (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Tom Killefer: Outgoing, 1937 Sept.-1938 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tom Killefer: Outgoing, 1938 Feb.-June (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - University of CA, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fresno State, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - USC, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - UCLA, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Washington, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Universities, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Associates, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - International Relations, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Pamphlets, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - N.S.F.A. Pt. I, Tom Killefer, Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - N.S.F.A. Pt. II, Tom Killefer:, Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Pre-Reg, Tom Killefer, Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Student Faculty Relations Committee, Tom Killefer: Incoming, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - President's Correspondence Pt. I, H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - President's Correspondence Pt. II, H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Corresp. Pt. I, H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee Corresp. Pt. II, H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "A-B", H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and N.S.F.A., H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, H.B. Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, K. Cuthberson, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence #2: Part I, K. Cutherberson, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence #2: Part II, K. Cuthberson, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Corresp., K. Cuthberson, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "F-K", K. Cuthberson, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "L", K. Cuthberson, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "N", K. Cuthberson, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - N.S.F.A., K. Cuthberson, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - N.S.F.A. Reporter, 1938-1940 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "P" / Stanford Fund, K. Cuthberson, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Other Universities, K. Cuthberson, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, K. Cuthberson, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "A-B", B. Jessup, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "C-F", B. Jessup, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "H-M", B. Jessup, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "N, Pt. I", B. Jessup, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - N.S.F.A. Reporter, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "N, Pt. II", B. Jessup, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "P-Y", B. Jessup, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "A-B", G. Jackson, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "C-D", G. Jackson, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "H-N", G. Jackson, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "O-U", G. Jackson, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - President's Report, G. Jackson, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Vice President's Report, (Patricia Adams), 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Student Manager's Report, E. Stamm, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "A-D", E. Stamm, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "E-N", E. Stamm, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "P-U", E. Stamm, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "W", E. Stamm, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Vice President's Report, J. McClanahan, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "A-B", J. McClanahan, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "C-D", J. McClanahan, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "E-J, J. McClanahan, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "L-N", J. McClanahan, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "P-W", J. McClanahan, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - President's Report / Miscellaneous Correspondence "A-B", R. Driscoll, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "C-H", R. Driscoll, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "L-M", R. Driscoll, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "N-T", R. Driscoll, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "U-W", R. Driscoll, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "A-B", B. White, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "C-D", B. White, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "E-F", B. White, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "H-J", B. White, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "M", B. White, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "P", B. White, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "R-V", B. White, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "A-C", R. Kennedy, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "D-L", R. Kennedy, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "M-N", R. Kennedy, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "P-W", R. Kennedy, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, R. Kennedy, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "A-B", M. Anderson, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "C-G", M. Anderson, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "H-I", M. Anderson, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "M", M. Anderson, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "N-P", M. Anderson, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "S-U", M. Anderson, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "V-W", M. Anderson, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Report to M. Anderson from I. I. R., 1947 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "A-D", A. Harris, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "E-I", A. Harris, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "L", A. Harris, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "M", A. Harris, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "N-P", A. Harris, 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "S-W", A. Harris, 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1949-1950: Rosin, Henry E., A-D (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1949-1950: Rosin, Henry E., E-F (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1949-1950: Rosin, Henry E., G-Z (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1950-1951: Buttner, Edgar M., A-B (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1950-1951: Buttner, Edgar M., B-C (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1950-1951: Buttner, Edgar M., D-N (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1950-1951: Buttner, Edgar M., O-Z (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1951-1952: Alley, Wayne, A-F (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1951-1952: Alley, Wayne, G-K (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1951-1952: Alley, Wayne, K-Z (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Report of VP Nancy Erwin, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Weisman, Richard, A (part 1), 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Weisman, Richard, A (part 2), 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Weisman, Richard, B-Z, 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Lozabnick, Donald D., A-D, 1953-1954 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Lozabnick, Donald D., E-M, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Lozabnick, Donald D., N-Z, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Report of the Student Body Pres. Donald D. Lozabnick, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Documents and Speeches, Peter Bing, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "A-B", P. Bing, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "F-L", P. Bing, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "M", P. Bing, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "N", P. Bing, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "P", P. Bing, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "R-U", P. Bing, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "U-W", P. Bing, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Report of ASSU President Jerry M. Messner, 1955 Summer (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Ralph, George W., 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Freelan, Robert E., A-E, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Freelan, Robert E., F-L, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Freelan, Robert E., P-W, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Messinger, James, A-C, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Messinger, James, D-L, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Messinger, James, miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Messinger, James, N-R, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Messinger, James, S-Z, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bohn, John, A-B, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bohn, John, C-D, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Bohn, John, E-H, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Bohn, John, Institute for International.Relations, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Bohn, John, J-N, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Bohn, John, P, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Bohn, John, R-S, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Bohn, John, St, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Bohn, John, U-Z, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Bohn, John, report, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Sundeen, Richard, A-D, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Sundeen, Richard, E-I.I.R., 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Sundeen, Richard, inter-University to NSA, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Sundeen, Richard, Pa-Po, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Sundeen, Richard, Pr-Z, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Sundeen, Richard, Report, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Royse, Larry, A-D, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Royse, Larry, E-Z, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "A", A. Rosencranz, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "C-F", A. Rosencranz, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "G-I", A. Rosencranz, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "H-L", A. Rosencranz, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "N-PE", A. Rosencranz, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "PR-R", A. Rosencranz, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence "S", A. Rosencranz, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - S. McBride, 1964 Sept.-Oct. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - S. McBride, 1964 Nov.-Dec. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - S. McBride, 1965 Jan.-Feb. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - S. McBride, 1965 March-April (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - S. Mc Bride, 1965 May-June (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Vice-President's Correspondence, M. A. Odegaard, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Mackenzie, William, A-K, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Mackenzie, William, L-Y, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Mackenzie, William, 1965 April-Oct. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Mackenzie, William, 1965 Nov.-Dec. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Mackenzie, William, 1966 Jan.-Feb. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Mackenzie, William, 1966 May-June (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Harris, David, Apr-Aug, 1966 April-Aug. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Harris, David, Sept-Oct, 1966 Sept.-Oct. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Harris, David, Nov-Dec, 1966 Nov.-Dec. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Harris, David, Jan-Feb., 1967 Jan.-Feb. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Harris, David, letter of resignation and clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Collins, M. J., 1967 March-May (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Lyman, Peter, 1967 May-Aug. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Lyman, Peter, 1967 Sept.-Nov. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Massarenti, Cesare, Dec.-Feb., 1967 Dec.-1968 Feb. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Massarenti, Cesare, March-June, 1968 March-June (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Hayes, Denis, correspondence re university committees, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Hayes, Denis, A-G, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Hayes, Denis, H-P, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Hayes, Denis, R-Y, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Hayes, Denis, outgoing letters A-G, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Hayes, Denis, outgoing letters H-P, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Hayes, Denis, outgoing letters R-T, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Hayes, Denis, outgoing letters W-Z, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Assorted proposals and miscellaneous correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Vice-president's correspondence, von Schlegell, Victor, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 1969-1970 Council of Presidents, John Grube (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 1969-1970 Council of Presidents, Barry Askinas (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 1969-1970 Council of Presidents, Patrick Shea (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 1969-1970 Council of Presidents, Joyce Kobayashi (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - 1970-1971 Council of Presidents (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - 1970-1971 Council of Presidents (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 1970-1971 Council of Presidents: Reports (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - ASSU Council of Presidents Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Council of Presidents Correspondence, Elaine Wong, Scott Burke, Peter Van Pelten, Brent Appel, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Council of Presidents records, Elaine Wong, Scott Burke, Peter Van Pelten, Brent Appel, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Council of Presidents Correspondence and records, O'Grady, Friend, Garfield, Ogletree, 1974 Jan.-April (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Council of Presidents Correspondence and records, O'Grady, Friend, Garfield, Ogletree, 1973 Sept. - Dec. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Council of Presidents Correspondence and records, O'Grady, Friend, Garfield, Ogletree, 1973 May-Aug. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Council of Presidents Chronological correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Council of Presidents Chronological correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Council of Presidents, 1979-1984 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Council of Presidents 80-81, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - ASSU Council of Presidents Meetings, Information 81-82, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Council of Presidents 82-83, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - ASSU Council of Presidents, 1968-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - ASSU Council of Presidents, 1967-1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Council of Presidents Projects and Issues (1 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Council of Presidents Projects and Issues (2 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - ASSU: Council of Presidents Orientation, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - ASSU: Council of Presidents Orientation, 1970-1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Vice President's Report 1958-59 (pt. a), 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Vice President's Report 1958-59 (part b), 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Vice President's Report 1959-1960 (part a) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Vice President's Report 1959-1960 (part b) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - President's Report 1963-1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - President's Report 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Secretary Notes, 1919-1923 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Secretary Notes, 1923-1928 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Secretary Notes, 1932-1936 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Secretary Notes, 1936-1940 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Applications (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Legislative, Series 2
  Legislative records contain agendas, minutes, memoranda, resolutions, reports, correspondence and other materials of the ASSU Senate and various committees; the ASSU constitution and by-laws along with revisions and amendments; election handbooks and other election materials; and files on the Honor Code, the Student Conduct Legislative Council, and the judicial system in general.
  - Cabinet Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - LASSU Committee on Religion Report, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Senate Materials, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agenda and minutes, 1970-71 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Attendance and voting records, 1970-71 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Bills, 1970-71 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Resolutions, 1970-71 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Committee reports, 1970-71 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - President's reports, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Senate roster, 1970-71 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Senate Minutes and agendas, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Attendance and voting records, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Senate resolutions, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Senate committee reports, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ASSU Report on Committee and the Intern Program, compiled by Diane Fields and Ann Kimball, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Nominations Committee, 1969-72 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Senate Meetings: agendas, minutes, memos, etc. (1 of 3), 1972-73 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Senate Meetings: agendas, minutes, memos, etc. (2 of 3), 1972-73 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Senate Meetings: agendas, minutes, memos, etc. (3 of 3), 1972-73 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Standing Rules of the ASSU Senate (in use 1972-73), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Agenda and minutes, 1972-73 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Senate resolutions and bills, 1972-73 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Senate materials 1973-74: Members and bylaws (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Senate materials 1973-74: Agendas and minutes (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Senate materials 1973-74: Agendas and minutes (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Senate materials 1973-74: Amendments to Constitution, new bylaws, resolutions (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Senate materials 1973-74: committee reports and bills (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Senate materials 1973-74: ASSU budget (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Senate 1973-74, Dave Marin: Standing Rules and bylaws (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Senate 1973-74, Dave Marin: Meetings, October (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Senate 1973-74, Dave Marin: Meetings, November (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Senate 1973-74, Dave Marin: Meetings, January, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Senate 1973-74, Dave Marin: Meetings, February, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Senate 1973-74, Dave Marin: Meetings, March, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Senate 1973-74, Dave Marin: Meetings, April, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Senate 1973-74, Dave Marin: Meetings, May, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Committes, 1973-74 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Senate materials (1 of 3), 1974-75 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Senate materials (2 of 3), 1974-75 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Senate materials (3 of 3), 1974-75 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Senate Meeting Files: Agenda and minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Senate Meeting Files: President's Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Senate Meeting Files: Financial Manager's reports, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Senate Meeting Files: committees, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Senate Meeting Files: miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - ASSU: Nominations Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Senate Meeting Files: Agenda and minutes, 1975-76 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Senate Meeting Files: Chair Committee reports, 1975-76 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Senate Meeting Files: Council of Presidents, 1975-76 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Senate Meeting Files: Financial reports, budgets, 1975-76 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Senate Meeting Files: Resolutions and bills, 1975-76 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Senate 1976-1977 I (Oct.-Nov. meetings) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Senate 1976-1977 II (Jan.-Feb. 7 meetings) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Senate 1976-1977 III (Feb.14-March meetings) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Senate 1976-1977 IV (April-June meetings) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Senate Meeting File 1976-1977: minutes (Box 5, Folder 5)